Here are problems that I found that... Well, you fix them. You guys know what you're doing.

Shifter:

- Icons for the shifting feats seem to be turned around a bit... I don't quite know what's up with them, but they don't entirely look right.
- Uh... Okay, every time an ability is used, it seems to say something about the harper mage or mage killer. Unless it's returning to your true form, of course. Then, you get a nice recap of the ENTIRE PROFILE of the Mage Killer.
-I REALLY do need a list of everything that can be turned into as an epic shifter... or at least some way to figure it out, aside from random testing. And don't forget what can be turned into as an epic shifter but not the normal shifter... or something like that... I just need a way to figure it out. When testing, I was sorely confused. I also need to know what is case sensitive in the commands and such.

Lich:

-Same deal with the word problems. Use certain abilities, get names of other classes. Please check that...

More will be added as I accidently find them. I'm not actually testing here, I'm just... well, trying to figure out what the heck some of these abilities do so I can redocument them.


***********NOTE: I am not sure if these problems are still in the current version! I am working off the old version, as this one's a bit messy. If this IS fixed, let me know and I'll erase it. I just needed to know for what I was doing.